claymont.com 2016-01-09

# Claymont Search Engine-free search engine submissions

| 

**_Summary_**

Claymont respects and protects the privacy of those that use Claymont's search engine services ("Claymont Search Services"). Claymont will not sell your email address to anyone without your express permission and we control all e-mail delivery to assure your privacy. Claymont gathers certain types of information about individuals that use the Claymont Search Services (“Users”). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") applies only to online transactions, activity and email communications. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information we gather and how we use it. Please be aware that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so by law in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this Privacy Policy. When we do share information with our partners and advertisers, it is in aggregate form, and does not identify you personally. Claymont does not collect or use any information about you except for the information that you provide or is publicly available, and this information is used solely to make the services provided more relevant to your interests. By becoming a Claymont User, you agree to the Claymont Terms and Conditions. This includes your agreement to receive email announcements, updates and other carefully screened special offers and promotions. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may remove your email from the Claymont database by sending a request to support@claymont.com and your web site will no longer be listed in the Claymont Search Engine.  

**_Claymont and Cookies_**

Upon your first visit to Claymont, Claymont sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. Claymont uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to understand our user base more. Claymont does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search. Claymont will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Be aware, however, that some parts of the Claymont Search Service may not function properly if you refuse cookies. 

**_What Information Do We Collect?_**

Claymont does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. Claymont notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. For example, Claymont may use your IP address or browser language to determine which language to use when showing search results or advertisements.

**_Third-Party Advertisement Servers_**

Some of our advertisers use third-party companies to serve their advertisements on our site. Often, these third-party advertising companies employ cookie and visitor activity technologies to measure advertisement effectiveness. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Use of their tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. If you would like more information about the privacy policies of the third-party advertising providers including information on how to opt out of their tracking methods, check their respective sites or send request to [support@Claymont.com](mailto:support@Claymont.com). 

_**Business Transfers**_

Claymont is always seeking to improve our website and Internet Business Services. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. In the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets or business of the company by, with, or into another company (a "Successor"), one of the assets which would generally be transferred is the information we collect from our members, customers, registrants, and users. However, the use of this information by any Successor would still be governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time, including any amendment after such transaction, and you will continue to have the right to opt-out of sharing your information with third parties. A Successor to our business is not considered to be a third party for these purposes. 

**_Links to Other Sites_**

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by Claymont Search Services are developed by people over whom Claymont exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Claymont may choose to exhibit its search results in the form of a "URL redirector." When Claymont uses a URL redirector, if you click on a URL from a search result, information about the click is sent to Claymont, and Claymont in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. Claymont uses this URL information to understand and improve the quality of Claymont's search technology. For instance, Claymont uses this information to determine how often users are satisfied with the first result of a query and how often they proceed to later results.

**_With Whom Does Claymont Share Information?_**

Claymont may share aggregate information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our Users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. For example, we may disclose how frequently the average Claymont user visits Claymont, or which other query words are most often used with a certain query word. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order.

**_Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy_**

By using the Claymont Search Services and our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms and Conditions. Claymont may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**_Who can I ask if I have additional questions?_**

Feel free to contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. You may notify us by either:

Writing to us at: ATTN: Customer Service  
Claymont  
381 Brinton Lake Road  
Thornton, PA 19373 

Emailing us at: [support@Claymont.com](mailto:support@Claymont.com)

|
